ezweb123.com 2016-05-14

# ezweb123.com – Privacy

Ezweb123.com has all data managed by SiteMaker Software Ltd who are our data controllers. The team at SiteMaker Software Ltd regards your privacy as very important. As required by the UK Data Protection Act 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of all information that you give us.

This statement describes the privacy policies of SiteMaker Software Ltd. We will not sell, share, rent or otherwise disclose your information to others in ways different to how they are disclosed in this statement.

What information do we collect and how do we use it?

Email Address:  
When you first register with us, we ask for your email address. Your email address is used to communicate important information about your account, such as payments due or to reset your password. In addition, if you have chosen to remain part of our mailing list, we send you our newsletter, and/or offers and promotions from ourselves or our carefully selected partners about products or services that are relevant to you. At the end of our newsletters or offers, we always provide you with the opportunity to remove yourself from our mailing list. Additionally, you may opt in or out of either of these types of mailing from any site by clicking My Details from the control bar of any site to which you are logged in, and select Edit my Details. Where your email address has been shared with one of our partners, they are also bound by the terms of this privacy policy and any communications from them will include instructions on how to be removed from their list.

If you choose to become a member of one our customers' sites, you are agreeing to disclose your email address to that site leader. Through SiteMaker, a site leader can choose to mail individual members, groups of members or the entire membership of the site. When you join, you can choose to not be part of the mailing list, and in addition you can always choose to remove yourself from the mailing list of a site by using the unsubscribe function at the end of every email sent from the SiteMaker system.

If you are logged in to any site, and choose to post information, your posting will by default also include your email address. You are able to remove or edit this address before you submit your posting. In addition, you may choose to be notified by our system of replies or updates in which case your email address will again be used. 

If you build a site with us, you provide a site email address that is published on your site as a way of contacting the site owner. This defaults to your email address, but can be updated through Manage your site.

Personal Information, Browser Details and Login Times

If you choose to subscribe to SiteMaker, we ask you some additional personal questions such as your age, gender, occupation, postal/ZIP code and country. We also collect data about your browser, login times and IP addresses when you visit any SiteMaker sites.

This information is only used in aggregated form – no user is individually identifiable from the data we disclose. It is used by us to understand our customers better and to ensure we focus our development on satisfying the needs of our users. We may also use this information in working with our partners in describing our customer base to ensure the products and services that we or our partners may offer are relevant.

Information Within Sites

In creating your site with SiteMaker, you may include personal identifiable information in your site. This is entirely at your own responsibility and SiteMaker Software Ltd are in no way liable for the disclosure of this information. SiteMaker Software Ltd reserves the right to promote from time to time sites built with SiteMaker. However, in these cases we will make reasonable efforts to obtain the consent from the site leader in advance.

Credit/Debit Card Details, Billing Address and Payment History

We have partnered with Worldpay Plc for the handling of all credit card payments. When you pay by credit or debit card, you are asked for your card details and billing address. This information is held exclusively by Worldpay, and you agree to their privacy policy ([available here](http://www.worldpay.com/about_us/index.php?page=privacy "Worldpay privacy policy")) in completing the payment steps. SiteMaker Software Ltd have no access to your card details, but they do have access your billing address and payment history in order to assist with customer service enquiries. Under no circumstances are these details disclosed to any third parties.

Police Investigation

Any of the information collected by us may be disclosed to the authorities as part of any investigations into any illegal activities that may take place on the SiteMaker service, as governed by UK law.

What about cookies?

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer. Only the information that you provide, or the choices you make while visiting a Web site, can be stored in a cookie. Allowing a Web site to create a cookie does not give that or any other site access to the rest of your computer, and only the site that created the cookie can read it. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do allow us to remember your login details and therefore offer you a personalized service without you having to log in on every visit. If you prefer not to use cookies, you can choose not to have your login details remembered on logging in or you can disable the feature in your browser.

Your Consent

By registering with SiteMaker and using our services, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us in the ways detailed above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. If you have any specific questions about our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://support.ezweb123.com/anonymous_requests/new "Contact us").
